Presented by Cinema Service Co., Ltd.
In association with CJ Entertainment Inc.
Produced by Cine2000
Executive Producer
KANG Woo-suk
Associate Producers KIM In-soo,
KIM Joo-sung, KIM Dong-hyun
Perfect! 100%
UHM Jung-hwa
HAN Chae-young
Let's call it a day!
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
PARK Yong-woo
We'll decide on the Dubai case
at the meeting tomorrow.
See you at 9.
LEE Dong-gun
Where are you?
Hi, where are you?
I'm on my way.
Where are you?
Hey, I'm awfully tired.
I've arrived early.
Just to check on the place.
I totally have to be there, hon.
Yeah, love ya.
See you soon.
Producer LEE Mi-young
Line Producer NAM Jung-iI
Just a habit, you know.
LOVE NOW
Thank you,
Director JUNG Yoon-su
thank you for coming.
Yeah, go straight up.
Shit.
Uh... What's wrong with this?
Can you pretend you didn't
see me fooling around?
I'll confess. l promise.
Hey, Min-jae.
When did you arrive?
Hey.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks, pal.
Nice suit.
You two guys haven't met?
This here's Park Young-jun.
He's the blue chip in the
business right now.
- VP of Mano Development, conceptualizing...
- That'll do. Let's not go into details.
- Nice meeting you.
- He's a detailed guy, you know.
Min-jae here.
I'm the blue chip of his life.
- You call that a joke?
- Can I sit over there?
Yeah, the sofa's all yours.
Hold on.
Oh, and this lady here
has supervised all the lighting in here.
She's Young-jun's wife.
I'm So-yeo.
l'm Min-jae.
Hey, Mi-sun.
Hi, guys.
- Hey, Mi-sun.
- Yeah?
You look breathless today.
It's not the first time, you know.
Isn't the lighting
perfect in here?
Doesn't So-yeo look
prettier today?
She's always the same.
Wow- congratulation.
My god!
This place looks great!
Hi, guys.
Hello, long time no see.
Where are these guys anyway?
Over here.
Why are you saying hi to
people you don't know?
Congratulation! Congratulation!
You've finally
become a bar owner!
10 years of buying drinks
for you is over. Payback time!
Of course! Two visits a week
guaranteed. Okay?
Yeah, but no credits.
I'm so happy for you.
This is really great!
- Hi hon.
- You're late.
Oh dear.
Everyone, sit, sit.
That was a noisy entrance.
I couldn't help but notice this fella.
He's my husband.
Oh, hello.
This place is gorgeous.
- Looks great, huh?
- Yeah.
Sir!
- Hey there.
- Come on in.
Hello, sir. You didn't have
trouble with the traffic?
- Yeah, it was fine.
- You didn't bring you wife?
Why bother.
Hey, Young-jun.
Have you two acquainted?
i told you about her.
She's Seo Yu-na, and she'll
provide you the VlP service.
The best we have
in our department.
Thank you.
I thought you had
a leg problem.
You must be feeling the weight on your
shoulders with such an important role.
I've heard a lot about you.
I'm Seo Yu-na.
No need to feel pressured.
With so much work, you won't have
time for shopping.
Your wife's pretty busy too.
i can't wear what others
choose for me. You know that.
That's precisely
why you need her.
Who would think you're the owner
of Mano Development?
People have to get suited to
their standards.
I've put you on the VlP list.
You'll be in good hands.
I'll do my best.
Hey, Min-jae.
You should be able to help So-yeo.
I'm sorry?
I heard about your
business trip to Hong Kong.
It's high season,
and there won't be any rooms left.
- You have one of your chain hotels there, right?
- Yeah.
It's okay.
She won't need that.
Hey, where's the love?
It's all about helping out, you know.
Go on, you should help her.
This'll pay you back.
Oh.
You owe her a favor?
No, what l meant was...
What's this about?
Hey, that tastes great.
You two sure work like a couple.
Don't bother.
Hey, we're not regular guests.
-Trying to sneak out without paying, huh?
- That's called teamwork.
Hush, everyone.
So-yeo, does this guy get
any sleep at all?
He's always like this
at gatherings.
I knew it. So what should
we do about this?
- What are you doing?
- There he goes again.
Don't!
- It didn't go in.
- It didn't?
The fruits look nice.
Didn't that couple look
great together?
I envy them.
Envy them?
It must be herjob.
She has her husband well-dressed.
Yeah, it's herjob...
...to bother other
people with what they wear.
Where's my passport...
Now that you're back,
it's my turn to go.
When will we...
Time for a foot massage!
lt's time for my lovely wife
to get a foot massage.
Don't do that with
people around you.
Do what?
You can be a little
more stuck-up, you know.
Like Park Young-jun?
Exactly.
Did that look good to you?
That was more rude than anything.
I got a cast on my neck!
i pity her wife.
You pity her?
Didn't she look a little gloomy?
You sure had your eyes on her.
So you want to help her?
You don't have to get all snappy.
You wouldn't call that help.
i mean...
what is there to pity her?
You've heard about her husband, right?
Number 2 at Mano Development.
Number 2!
When have you been number two
in you life, huh?
How come your feet becomes
more beautiful with age?
And her side of the family owns
the nation's largest light bulb company.
So she's got a rich husband,
and comes from a rich family
plus she's a lighting designer with
her own shop at such an early age.
So what part do you pity
about her, huh?
Right, right!
So I'm wrong about that part.
Damn, l'm tired.
I think l'm getting old.
Are you just a nice guy,
or is itjust being naive?
Aren't you envious at all?
There you go, getting all snappy again.
Why should I be envious?
Hey, that's precisely why we're in this
miserable state, you know?
Oh, come on.
What's wrong with us?
I quit.
Hey.
We won't see each other
when i go on the business trip.
Let go.
Oh, come on Yu-na.
Hey, Yu-na.
You're getting less allowance from now on.
End of the conversation!
Hey, how can you do this to me?
You know how tight my budget is.
You're not the only one.
I wear sample wardrobe, remember?
We're not doing that badly.
Right?
Oh, let go. You're tickling me!
Okay, okay. Deal!
But you've got to fancy me.
Oh, be real.
What is there to fancy you about?
Damn it.
I'm good looking.
And I'm good at bed!
Let's see you get to work, tiger!
Bonsoir- So-yeo!
Beautiful So-yeo.
This is shop access card and
the address and the password here.
Thank you very much.
Are you sure you want to check
the light tonight again?
Of course, it's my job. I wanna
make sure everything works fine.
Magnifique!
Have Kim come up here.
She's been waiting for a long time.
It's not her first time here, either.
Hello.
Oh. Come on in, then.
Tell Kim to come up
10 minutes later.
i would say you enjoy wearing
a mix-and-match style.
You wear a tie, but with a
leather blouson instead of a jacket.
Or a suit with a shirt
but with no tie.
An unbalanced look suits well
with your personality.
But does not give you the
image of a CEO.
I don't wish to advertise
myself as a CEO.
I'm not talking about a style
that's too edgy,
as if you've just come down
from the catwalk.
Suits today come in a lot of
different patterns,
from active to traditional.
A man named Alexander Eckhart
once said,
'There are two types
of men in this world,
Those thatjust wear a suit,
and those that wear them the right way.'
You should start wearing suits
the right way,
with that classic...
Let's go with this, this,
and this.
30 inch waist,
100 for the chest,
38 and 'large',
American size.
Is Kim waiting right now?
Yes, sir.
Tell him to come up here.
We wouldn't lose face in front of
director Kang
if I buy two ltalian suits.
I'm not here to just sell
a couple of suits.
Consider myself
your fashion consultant.
So, I need to buy more suits?
No, that's not what I mean.
There's a briefcase
that I'd like to recommend.
All right then.
Send along the briefcase.
Something not too boring, though.
Okay.
Thank you for your time.
Let me know if
you need anything else.
When do you want your suit?
Whenever you feel convenient.
l'm not in a hurry.
Right.
You can find your way out, right?
Too much work on my shoulders,
you know.
That young son of a bitch!
You're from a good breed, huh?
Please consider our proposal.
It will be great for you, great for me.
OK, sure...
Tomorrow will be another long day.
I'm ok! I'm a tough guy.
Excuse me just a moment...
Oh yeah, no problem...
Why do l need a reason to
have a drink?
You can't fool me, girl.
You're in a bad mood tonight.
I am not.
Give me another shot!
Wow. This guy must really be someone
to make you feel this mad.
He's not worth a crap.
There you go again.
Who is this fella?
Your pal.
My pal? Which pal?
Young-jun?
Let's not talk about this.
Oh, we meet again!
Hey, you...
What brings you here Young-jun?
Never heard you were coming.
One of my appointments
were cancelled,
so I thought I'd drop by
for a drink.
That's great! We were getting
a little bored, the two of us.
Take a seat! Let's drink!
Uh, come sit over here...
I'll be at the bar.
Talk to you later.
No, no, no.
Drink with us, come on!
I'm interrupting
your conversation.
No, really! We were bored.
Hey, join us.
Don't be so shy.
You've all been acquainted,
let's drink.
We were getting so bored.
Sit. Have a drink.
Come on, sit over here.
That was close...
Chul-ju, let's drink some wine.
Alright.
This is a dish made
from a fish called Garupa.
This fella here looks
just like my boss.
And this is the Mantis shrimp,
very sweet flesh.
We're even with this treat,
you know.
Could I ask you another favor?
Sure! What can I do for you?
I have to check on the lights
but I don't know my way
around here.
Can I have a look at that?
- I have no idea where this is.
- I think... it's over that side.
You would look good on a
very formal suit, you know.
Why don't you try a classic London
Savile Row-style tailored suit?
You would look awesome in that.
While dress shirt matched
with a silk tie,
and a navy color two-button suit or...
A three-button suit
would be a safer choice,
if you're looking to succeed in business!
Perfect.
One hundred percent!
Does everyone in your business
talk like that?
Huh?
You seem to mix in
English all the time.
It sounds pretty retarded when
you use English like that on a sentence.
Don't you think?
Well... Most trend-setting
nations do speak English.
So it is hard to find the
right expression in Korean.
So if i want to
buy something from you,
I'll have to make a 'reservation'
with a 'phone call', right?
Do you have meals every now and
then with your 'clients'?
Oh, in you business...
You would call it 'lunch'.
You would do 'business'
and share 'love'.
You're right.
But the next stage
is the same for every business.
Next stage?
Yeah, the stage after 'love'.
'Sex'!
People in your business do that, right?
To think of it, you guys
at the construction business
would be involved in an intercourse
than have sex, right?
Hey, what's this about sex?
There's an air of lewdness here
that I haven't sensed before.
I'll leave you guys to talk.
No, you would actually 'copulate'.
But we folks using English
in between have 'sex'
or 'fuck'!
Leaving already?
Should be the next block ahead.
What did you say to
piss her off like that?
Nothing much.
You toyed with her
in the afternoon too?
Toy her? She's no toy,
you know.
Yu-na looks confident
but she is having a hard time.
Give her a break!
She supports both Min-jae
and her family,
and her sister got swindled
in marriage.
Be nice to her.
She's not a stranger.
Don't want to hear about it.
Oh...
You want someone to drive you home?
Or do you want to take a cab?
Give her a break, man.
Look at her!
Shit, it's cold.
Yu-na.
SEO Yu-na!
What do you think you're doing?
Let go!
Or you drunk or are you mad?
It's something expensive!
And it's not mine.
A little rain won't harm anything.
I'll buy it off you.
Have you been such
an ass all along?
Let's finish the conversation.
Finish what? Do you want to
get beat by a girl?
I buy a suit off you
and you want to beat
that client, huh? All right!
Huh? Hey!
Pretty, isn't it?
It's still a prison to the birds.
But doesn't that look sincere?
Trying to keep a bird
that one loves, and
at least trying to keep the bird
in a pretty cage.
So... let's put it this way.
I'd like to be beat with the
prettiest lash if I'm being tortured.
Or be stuck with a golden spear.
If I'm to die.
Let's find the shoe store first.
We can come back here tomorrow.
Not tomorrow.
I'm leaving on a morning flight.
Too bad.
Are you always this
quick in giving up?
But there's no other solution!
What if I come up with one?
You don't believe in me?
What are doing?
Min-jae!
it's okay.
No one's going to look anyway.
Don't be a fool.
I'm going for it.
What do you think you're doing?
Ha, fooled you.
It's over here.
Enough with fooling around.
I'll get you a cage.
You can't fool me twice.
This time it's for real.
Go ahead.
All right, you said it.
Here goes.
Can't stop it now.
What have you done?
Sorry, sorry sir...
i'm calling the police!
I'm sorry.
That wasn't on purpose.
So-yeo,
run!
No, no, this way!
What's wrong?
Take one step at a time.
We didn't even break the window,
what's with him?
My sentiments exactly.
- Here.
- Right...
How's your ankle?
Did you sprain it?
Yeah... it's okay.
You sure?
Yeah. See?
He's still following us!
What?
Don't leave me behind!
So-yeo. No one's following us.
So-yeo, it's a lie!
What are we here for?
You said you wanted to beat me up.
Let's see who beats up who.
Feel free to come up here.
We, at Fight Club,
will take full responsibility.
Come up and relieve your stress,
and you'll be eligible
for lots of prizes.
As the ring announcer,
I will give you one last chance...
For the first time ever,
a beautiful lady is
approaching the ring.
Man, you guys are lucky tonight!
Welcome!
This way, ma'am.
Standing at 5'7'',
with a bodacious bodyline.
The Jean D'arc of mixed martial arts...
And it looks like
she's pointing at someone...
This guy's a loser if he doesn't
stand to the challenge.
i'd love to get beat
by this beauty here.
Come on! Loser!
Well, what do you know.
Here's our man stepping in!
I'm not letting you off
because you're a girl.
Beat me and talk trash.
All right. Fight!
Fight me, you chicken!
Did you just hit me?
Hey, it's a full moon.
So-yeo, have you ever
experienced this? You know...
What did l think of that night,
to do such a crazy thing?
During those nights,
there always seems to be a full moon.
That's mean of them.
Why make an excuse on a full moon?
So-yeo,
have you ever had a date with
a man other than your husband,
at a place you've come
for the first time?
No.
You see, that would be
an unusual event.
You look up the sky, and...
there you have it.
Is that for real?
- So-yeo.
- Yeah?
You look better with your hair down.
Wow.
Sorry. l've got to check on the lights,
because the shop opens tomorrow.
i know this singer.
You do?
The guy who sang the song...
His friend's brother's roommate
was close with...
My mother's secret boyfriend.
Hold on.
His friend's brother's...
Whoa, that's a real destiny.
Do you know that
when a woman has a secret...
she's bound to tell
that to one certain person?
You shouldn't tell our secret.
Our secret? What secret?
We almost broke someone's window.
That's a little lame for a secret.
Huh?
One shot!
Come on, spit it out.
What is your problem?
There's something you've
got figured all wrong.
Figured all wrong?
So I was hoping to
teach you what's right.
Ha. Teach me?
A while ago you've mentioned...
That it's sex after datingfor everyone.
You're wrong.
We have sex first.
Then we decide whether
we'll date or not.
Sex is just sex.
There's no need to date.
Treating something,
buying flowers...
You do that to take a girl into bed.
You've got that right.
Are you hitting on me?
lf i am...
Will you fall for it?
What would l do
with a kid like you?
It says it all in your face.
I FEEL DESPERATE.
Good night.
Have a safe trip back to Seoul.
Where would you people
have sex without us
in the construction business?
We make that possible
because we provide the space
Don't you think?
So you'll build hotels naked
without us?
Let's see you do it.
With your thing bouncing up and down.
Don't bother me after
you've had a taste of me.
We do it full time,
with 45 minute halves.
Soccer?
Ha. We do a marathon.
We start
when the marathon starts,
all the way till the last guy
crosses the finish line.
No breaks in between.
Did you know that?
Bad killer instincts
and shooting touch...
If that's how bad you are,
don't even try playing the match.
Fair play!
If you're into having
all the fun for yourself,
you won't leave this place alive.
Understand?
Fair play?
That's a good term.
Don't get all dirty after
we go through the game.
What?
Don't pester me
with stupid demands.
I knew it.
Filthy blue collars.
That's the mentality
that you guys have.
Did the other girls want something
else after they hop into bed with you?
It must've been real bad,
wanting something else in return.
It was a joke.
Don't get all bitchy about that.
Let go! You disgust me.
You feel your
stamina wilt with age,
your skin goes dull,
and when there's nothing left
to charm the guys,
that's when you're done with.
So the great Oh Mi-sun
will get married
before she's done with?
No, it's just a thought!
It passed through my mind, you know.
Will Chul-ju marry you?
Who said l was marrying him?
What?
You mean there's someone else?
Drink.
Huh? l envy you, Mi-sun.
It's for you.
Seo Yu-na speaking.
Hello?
It's Young-jun here.
Another staff has been
assigned to you.
And who's call was that?
I don't see the need of continuing
our conversation.
Who is it?
No need to know.
i haven't seen you talk
that mean before.
No way it's a client of yours.
Something's fishy here...
Seo Yu-na here.
Thank you for calling.
I'll call back in 10 minutes.
Promise!
Seo Yu-na here.
Thank you for calling.
Perfect timing.
I just arrived.
What's with your voice?
What about it?
Aren't you glad to hear my voice?
I feel tired, that's all.
Look over the
11 o'clock direction.
- Did you have a hard time?
- Huh?
Yeah, couldn't sleep well.
I think I've caught a cold.
What about you?
How did you fare without me?
i missed you.
More than any other instance.
Don't switch it off.
How am I?
I'm sorry?
To women.
How do I fare as a man?
You're sick.
What?
An asshole too.
That's a little rude.
Hey...
Am I really that sick?
Do i look better
with my hair tied up or down?
Turn off the lights.
This isn't the first time,
you know.
I swear this will be
the last time. 30 grand.
Then your sister
will get the divorce.
i'm busy.
Don't call me with stuff like this.
Hey, hey!
It's a call for you.
Park Young-jun?
- This is for Ms. Kim. Hold onto it.
- Okay.
Hello?
Does the buyer usually have to
Iook for the seIIer?
I thought I had told you
that there's someone else for you.
I need something for an event.
l'll let the new personnel...
No need.
I want you to choose my wardrobe.
I'II have to hang up, I'm busy.
- Hyun-kyung, this one too.
- Yes.
You never know
what she'll look for.
Right.
Why record the voice
if you're not caIIing back?
Making people wait...
Keep your promise next time.
That's all.
Yes.
Mr. Park, you must be
having lunch?
Alone in your executive office?
Having sushi with a piIe of
paperwork by your side?
Take some time to Iook back
at yourself, Mr. Park.
You'll realize how lonely
and pathetic you are.
That'll be all.
There's a package for you.
Sir...
The sample for the gallery arrived
from the head office.
Aren't you going to take a look?
Sir.
Why let out a sigh in
front of food?
- Because l'm hungry.
- But you're not eating.
i'm eating. Look.
Satisfied?
Hey, check out
that girl over there.
She's eating all alone,
and without any soju.
She must've been dumped by a guy.
- I've been wanting to call you...
- Are you always this quick in giving up?
- See you tomorrow.
- Okay.