How about a truce at this stage?
You really are some client.
It's all my fault.
I beg for your forgiveness.
Getting drunk is a bad excuse.
We were both very sober.
So you really meant to treat me
like a whore?
You looked like a pro,
working up a guy
and leaving like that.
Is this the attitude of someone
who has come for truce?
You're the one playing down
on me right now.
I'm not interested. I've never
been treated like this before.
Move!
Seo Yu-na!
Are you out of your mind?
How can you speed in
a parking lot, lady?
I'm sorry.
Let's get this over with.
Doesn't seem like a
big accident to me.
Who're you, anyway?
I'm her guardian.
Guardian, bull shit.
She's no kid, you know.
Is he your husband?
No.
Who is he then?
- He's a stalker.
- What?
Stalker?
He's been spying on me
for a few days.
What nonsense are you talking?
He was waiting
for me in front of the office,
so l was trying to shake off him.
Seo Yu-na!
This is getting a little too
out of hand.
Are you serious?
You look pretty normal to me.
Just give him a warning.
I'll give him a good talk as well.
He does seem to listen to others...
so don't be too hard on him.
- Thank you, officer.
- Take care on your way back home.
What is he doing in there?
He must've done something wrong.
He should gladly pay for it, then.
Why didn't you tell us
in the first place?
Would you like some tea
before you leave?
Seo Yu-na!
Take care.
Stop right there!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you satisfied now?
You're damn right,
I'm satisfied.
So you got one back on me.
We're even now.
Okay?
Don't make a fool out of
other people, okay?
Why? It's fun.
Not to me.
All right, I admit that
I made a fool out of you.
But I don't do that to people
I don't care about!
This is the first time
I've done this...
Ever since I did it to
my neighbor when I was 10.
I swear.
What is it that you want?
I told you. A truce.
Is that all?
- Let's go for a truce first...
- Then what?
Haven't thought about it.
Hey, when people want to reconcile,
they try to flatter
or wait until the anger passes.
You can't flatter a girl, can you?
So let's just wait
until the anger passes.
Let's have some coffee.
I'm trying to flatter you,
that's all.
Hey, Seo Yu-na!
You've got some change?
Jung Min-jae!
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I had to meet someone here.
I was on my way home.
I'm going home too.
Yeah, I'm done.
- Let's go then.
- Right... What brought you here?
I had an appointment with someone.
I was on my way back.
Min-jae, does your heart still throb
when you see me?
Huh?
Does your heart still pound
when you look at me?
That was a little unexpected.
Why?
Come on, answer me.
Do you still feel that way?
Hold on. Let me see...
4 years of dating,
and 3 years of marriage...
...and we have a diagnosis.
If the heart is still beating like that,
it should be a heart disease.
Jung Min-jae, you insolent bastard.
Yu-na.
Don't call me.
You've hurt my feelings.
Make me go crazy about you again.
Do you really feel
that way about me now?
Hey, long time no see.
I've been looking for you all day.
And you weren't answering
my calls either.
Let's see... in 3 minutes,
It'll be exactly 24 hours.
I'm not in the mood
for a joke now.
I understand how you
would've felt last night.
But...
i can't guarantee that something like
that will not happen again.
There will be tougher times ahead.
Why are you telling me this?
i thought I had to tell you.
About your situation.
The circumstances and all.
And what difference will
that make?
Someone has to pull the plug.
What am I going to do?
i can't think of
anything but you, Min-jae.
Perfect. One hundred percent!
You leave me
and don't give a call?
Leave you? I went my way
and you went yours.
I got out of the way because
you might feel uncomfortable.
Uncomfortable? Why?
I thought we had a truce.
I thought I had told you that
I needed some time.
I'm not good at waiting.
I'll flatter you instead.
Well then, don't antagonize me.
What brings you here?
I'm here to see CHO Yu-na.
I'm CHOl Dong-sup.
She's not in.
Please step outside!
Who's that?
You don't need to know.
Tell your manager her sister's
husband is here to see her!
What's going on?
What is this all about?
- Wait. Don't do this.
- Hey, Seo Yu-na! This isn't funny at all.
- Please.
- Let's do business the safe way.
Shit, do you want your sister
to get in trouble?
Hey, you know what
your sister did to me?
I've been set up.
Set up real bad, you hear?
Let's call it a deal at 30 grand.
I'm a victim too, you know.
Take him outside!
Go change your suit.
I'll take it to your car.
Who's that?
Young-jun's step-mother.
Hello.
Hi, there.
Working so late?
What brings you here?
I was passing by and
saw the lights on.
Is he a new employee?
I'm from the construction company.
Is that right?
So-yeo, I'll talk to
you later then.
Right.
How's everything going?
Fine.
I'll be on my way then.
Leaving already?
Don't stay here till late at night.
Your husband won't like it.
I'll see you at
your father-in-law's birthday.
Take care.
It'll be okay.
Right. Nothing happened, really.
Let's go to Hong Kong.
Hong Kong?
It was great at Hong Kong, the two of us.
There's no one to recognize us...
Alright. I'm going to
Hong Kong right now!
Answer the phone, damn it!
So you're here to rake
in some cash?
You can't have it for free, though.
Call me.
Hey, Yu-na.
That's some pimp you have there.
What have you done?
No need to know.
Who do you think you are anyway?
Pretend you didn't see that.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Yeah.
Do I look pathetic to you?
Yeah. Pretty much.
I know you're crying
because you're flattered.
That'll be the last favor.
What do you mean?
It only has just started.
'Until we satisfy'.
There's nothing I can do
to return the favor.
Have I asked for anything?
You know... what I mean.
I can't leave my husband like this.
What about me?
You can't live without me?
No.
See what l mean?
Your husband will feel the same way.
You girls misjudge men.
Min-jae's not like you!
I really wanted to
flirt with you, Seo Yu-na...
Can I speak to Jung Min-jae?
I wish to thank him
for the arrangements.
Really?
Tell him to drop by
the members' lounge when he returns.
Or I'll go there to meet him.
All right. Thank you.
I'm telling you this
because I like So-yeo.
You've got to end this
sort of relationship.
Hmm. Right.
Did you make it out of the
ladies' room safely?
Of course.
What's that tone then?
Hmm?
You sound weary.
Must be a weak throat.
You shouldn't be calling...
With your husband around.
I've got something to do,
I won't be able to see you tonight.
Overtime work.
Let's talk Iater.
I thought you wouldn't pick up.
Should l hang up then?
That temper of yours...
Is everything aII right?
Yeah.
You alone?
Why should I be alone?
My husband's always by my side.
Like your wife is by your side,
Young-jun.
Thanks for reminding me.
I'll hang up since I've heard your voice.
Wait.
Don't eat by yourself!
Don't bother if you're not
going to eat with me.
Hang up.
There's a guest calling to order.
- Hey.
- Hey! You made it.
Hello!
Good to see you all.
So... Is everyone here?
We have an announcement to make.
We're getting married!
Who? You and me?
Right, I decided to let
you get married to me.
You should be proud!
Don't you think that's
a little too one-sided?
You're got the bar
and apartment mortgaged.
You need someone
to rescue your life.
Hey, you shouldn't believe entirely
what my father tells you.
Mi-sun, why get married
at the prime of life?
You've still got it all.
There's nothing to lose.
I would say the same
thing to Chul-ju.
There are younger girls
all over the place.
Not all men think like you do,
my dear.
Women these days aren't
like you either.
That's why I don't
bring her to gatherings.
Who made her come, anyway?
Stop toying with your cell phone.
What have you been doing?
What is it with you these days?
You're not like you used to be.
There are times, Yu-na.
Times? What times?
Forget it.
Something's strange today.
Should I have kept
the announcement for later?
It's not like we're
breaking up, you know.
Damn, what is it with you people?
Yu-na.
Am I doing the right thing?
I don't know...
One thing I'm sure of is that
it becomes quite boring as you live along.
Hey there's no couple more into
each other than you guys.
I just had to make him mine
when I first met him.
I could feel the passion
when I saw his face.
And you don't feel that now?
If you feel that now, you're ill.
Nothing excites me anymore.
Stop that.
I can see that your relationship
has reached its peak.
Pretty much.
What's up with you guys?
How are you guys?
Nothing has changed between us
after we got married.
Really?
I envy you guys.
I've never felt passionate
about him.
I'm beginning to like
this gathering!
Mr. Park.
What have you done to
make her say that?
Is not being passionat a bad thing?
There's no need to get all cold
if you're not passionate.
Jung Min-jae.
What is wrong with you?
Are you drunk?
I'm not saying that it's bad,
but it's not a good thing either.
What is this guy saying?
Min-jae!
Can I ask you something?
No, we'll talk later.
This is weird. Is there something
wrong with the drinks?
I'll go check.
Do we have bootlegs here?
Why does my stomach hurt?
Let's go home.
It looks original to me...
Why are you doing this to me?
The ladies' room is
on the opposite side.
I've never feared losing
what l have since
I started seeing you.
But it looks like you're
the one getting scared.
That's easy for you to say.
Is that because you're rich?
I haven't got much, and I've paid
a lot to earn what I have now.
That's why I'm scared
of losing them
I'm like that, you know.
I know you're doing
that on purpose
I'll wait at 'Beginning'.
Don't.
What are you doing?
Wait...
The toilet's blocked!
We get that often these days.
Use the one on the second floor.
Mi-sun, am I drunk?
You will be
if you drink at that rate.
Where's Min-jae?
How would I know?
I asked Yu-na.
You going?
I'm leaving too.
Yu-na. Sit here for a little while.
Mi-sun, talk to her!
Stay, Yu-na.
What's with you?
Sit down, girl!
Hey, let's have another drink.
Shit, I knew she wouldn't
listen to me.
Hey, forget it, I'm not getting
involved in this anymore!
Seo Yu-na!
Your husband...
If he says he'll be able to
live without you...
Can we make it happen?
Answer me.
No.
I can't live without him.
Chul-ju!
Hey.
I want to ask for a favor.
Min-jae must be
seeing someone else.
Talk him to end the relationship.
I owe you one.
They're close friends of yours.
I'm leaving.
Young-jun, hey!
Oh man...
Yu-na. What are you doing here?
Is that true?
What is?
About Min-jae seeing someone else.
Is that true?
Hey, Yu-na...
You should know better.
He can't live without you.
What do I do, Chul-ju?
What am I going to do?
Yu-na,
are you asleep?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
What for?
About being all petty...
not giving you enough pocket money...
I'm sorry.
Yu-na.
We both know that we've
come this far
because of you.
Min-jae,
let's have a baby.
You wanted that, right?
Yu-na,
I've got something to tell you.
I must be drunk.
Let's talk later.
Will you...
...hit me, Yu-na?
Aren't you coming to bed?
I've got a question to ask you.
Am I...
...really that cold-hearted?
Yeah. You didn't know?
That's what makes you attractive.
That's what I fell for too.
Can I ask something too?
Was...
I...
...a woman to you?
You're my wife.
But when you said
we were never passionate,
I realized that you were a woman.
When did you say you were
leaving for Hong Kong?
Next weekend.
Should I go with you?
You're just saying that, right?
Yeah.
Oh, beautiful night.
- That was some wedding ceremony!
- Thank you.
- You look wonderful, dear!
- Thank you so much.
You guys still haven't left?
You really want to drink, huh?
Here, have a drink. Come on.
Right. l'd be glad to!
So, you've settled everything?
Yeah. It's not easy doing
a son's duty.
What's not easy?
You've got a beautiful wife!
Now that l see it,
I wish l could get married again.
You guys won't die
for each other, right?
Of course not.
No, not at all.
You won't feel like a victim, then.
So you won't have
to hate each other.
felt like a victim
whenever he flirted.
That's why I hate him.
I couldn't show that to my kids,
so now l've got
a lump on my chest.
Why didn't you tell me
about this?
I couldn't bear watching you enjoy.
Man, this is why l didn't want
to bring her along.
Sir, don't live like that,
damn it.
What?
You really like the young ones,
don't you?
What's wrong with you?
Chul-ju!
Let's exchange partners if you're
so much into young girls.
What did you say?
Hey.
Everyone's changing partners,
So why not us?
Why you son of a...
Alright. Let's do it!
Are you drunk?
What's wrong with that?
You're doing it,
so why can't I do the same?
Hey, Chul-ju's drunk.
Take him to the hotel.
Let's go!
Hey, cut the crap.
I'll help you guys out, too.
I can't stand you guys
sulk any longer.
So I'll settle everything for you!
You know how?
I've got the solution right here.
Stop it. Are you crazy?
Yeah, I'm crazy.
You see, l had to pretend to
be naive all along,
that must've made me go mad.
I'm crazy. So what?
- Hey, Kang Chul-ju!
- Sir, sir!
We should swap too.
You like younger girls, right?
No, to think of it...
Let's all swap here. Okay?
Come here,
you little piece of shit!
- Settle down.
- Flirt, flirt!
I'm not marrying
a madman like that.
Well thought, Mi-sun!
Look at these guys over here...
They meet. They get bored.
So they look for someone else.
Min-jae here likes So-yeo...
And Young-jun here,
worries about Yu-na.
Bastard. l'm getting rid of
this ring right now!
Mi-sun. Mi-sun!
Don't do this!
- Let go!
- He's drunk, Mi-sun.
l said, let go!
Oh no!
Chul-jung's father passed away.
Yeah, I should go.
Want me to pick you up?
May Damiano KANG rest
in eternal peace.
Lord, hear our prayer.
May the Lord's words pass upon generations
to come,
these are the words of the gospel.
How's your sister doing?
Is she preparing for the wedding?
I don't know why she's
getting married again.
She should be happy now.
That's funny.
Who says marriage
guarantees happiness?
Was I happy before?
I don't even remember.
You can be mad about me, Yu-na.
But don't erase
all the good memories.
Do you still eat by yourself?
Yeah. I'm a loner.
I'm curious.
Why did you marry me?
I went to the construction site
and saw a girl on a suit
wearing a helmet.
You usually don't wear helmets
because it ruins your suit.
But this girl had a helmet on.
I wanted to find out
more about her.
So you came to see me
before the actual meeting?
Yeah.
So... We didn't start out
that bad either.
My car's over there.
Take care.
Bye.
See you guys later.
You lost your way on purpose
in Hong Kong, right?
What?
You were teasing me,
weren't you?
Who talked to me
about the full moon?
You're the one that called it
a lame secret.
I'm going to Hong Kong next month.
Lucky you.
Garupa and Mantis shrimp,
remember all that?
I'll think about it.
Who said l was taking you?